webdriverjs.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy policy - WebDriverJS

This privacy policy is for explaining the way that we([http://www.webdriverjs.com](http://www.webdriverjs.com/)) collects, uses and maintains the information collected from individual user. This privacy policy applies to the Site, products and services offered by WebDriverJS.

**Non personal identification data of the Visitors**

Like most website operators, WebDriverJS collects non-personal-identification data of the users that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how the visitors use our website. From time to time, We may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website.

**Personal identification data of the visitors**

Certain visitors to WebDriverJS choose to interact with WebDriverJS in ways that require WebDriverJs to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive WebDriverJS updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, WebDriverJS collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with WebDriverJs. We does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our website. For instance, WebDriverJs may monitor the most popular pages on the site. WebDriverJS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. WebDriverJS uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. WebDriverJS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of WebDriverJS’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**How we tend to protect your information**

We adopt applicable knowledge assortment, storage and process practices and security measures to guard against unauthorized access, alteration, speech act or destruction of your personal data, username, password, dealings data and knowledge keep on our website.

**Sharing your personal data**

We don’t sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification data to others. we may share generic aggregative demographic data not connected to any personal identification data concerning guests and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads could also be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie allows it to serve ads to Users supported their visit to our website and different sites on the web. DART uses “non in person acknowledgeable data” and will NOT track personal information regarding you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. you may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Privacy policy changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, WebDriverJS may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in WebDriverJS’s sole discretion. We encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please don’t use our website. Your continuing use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy are deemed your acceptance of those changes.
